The next problem
Okay, um, Ayumu.
I cannot wake up early in the morning even if I go to bed early at night. How can I get up early?
There you go.
This is a problem that will continue to plague you as you grow older, and it will never go away.
Well, do you set an alarm clock?
Yes, I do.
But it doesn't wake me up.
Yes, sir.
Yes, it's my problem too.
I think that's what Hiroyuki was talking about.
Hiroyuki was saying that...
People have their best time to wake up.
That way you don't have to stress about it.
You don't have to get up early in the morning.
It's best to wake up at a time that suits the child.
Yes, sir.
I guess he's talking about when you have to get up early.
I don't know.
How old is he now? He's six.
He's still going to school.
And you haven't started school late? No, not yet.
No, I haven't. No, I haven't. I haven't.
What do you do when you wake up?
My mom wakes me up.
You want to be able to wake yourself up.
I used to do that before I went to bed.
"What time do you want to wake up tomorrow?
I'd chant "6:00 a.m. tomorrow, 6:00 a.m. tomorrow, 6:00 a.m. tomorrow" a lot.
I'd wake up pretty well.I can get up pretty well.
See how you do.
Yes, sir.
I also set all the alarms on my phone in five-minute increments.
When I wake up at 6:00, I do 6:05, 6:10, 6:15.
Yes, sir.
You never know, do you, kid?
I can't get up even as an adult.
I give up.
Yes, sir.
There's a girl at school that I like.
How can I get to know her?
Oh, that's good.
Love.
You mean you can't talk
You mean you can't talk about what you like?
It's embarrassing.
I can't play.
I can't play because I'm nervous.
I've never been nervous about someone I really like until this age.
I don't know why I'm embarrassed. Why can't I just be myself and talk cheerfully because I like him?
But I'm afraid of that.
That's what I'm afraid of. Can you talk with other girls?
Yes, I can.
What?What?
Really?
Seriously?
Well, you should probably tell her that.
Tell me what?
Tell the girl you like.
I'm too nervous and embarrassed to talk.
But he really wants to talk to her.
I told her that.
"That's why you don't talk to me.
Maybe she'll try to talk to you.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Yeah. What? I have a feeling about that. Girls.
Sure. What about the girl army?
I can talk to them now. Yeah, I can talk to them.
Come on. You better speak up. - Yeah.
Yes, sir. - Are you okay? Is it solved? Solved?
I'm having a hard time.
And, you know, if you do research on girls you like...
I'm gonna find out what anime she likes.
Okay, okay.
I'm too naive to know what to say.
Hiyori, I was just telling you about a boy in my class.
Oh, you still have that problem, what is it?
Well, he's chasing me, and I'm the only one chasing him.
So, how do you keep him from being mean to you?
Is that mean?
Maybe they're chasing you because they like you.
You know how some people are, like, so childish?
You're a child.You're a child.
It's like they're mean to you because they like you.
There are a lot of people in that neighborhood, in that society.
It's not that they don't like you because they're lurking around.
Do you think it's just that one person that everyone hates?
Just one person?
He definitely doesn't hate me.
I think he likes me... and he's cute.
Thank you very much.
I'm aware of that.
I'll be answer
альную
I've been here since you were a little girl.
I have one http
Yes.
Yes, please think about Monokarta.
I'm really good at drawing.
What I want to do is something 3D, and I've been trying to do it for a while.
I can't tell. But is it okay? Even if you don't get it.
Then, is it a monocarta?
Mo!
I wanted to write "ex-winter snowfall", but...
I wanted to write "ex-winter back of the head.
But it was too difficult.
There's snow on the ground, but it's white, so it doesn't come across at all.
But what I wanted to say was "snow on the back of ex-winter season".
Oh, it's snowing.
I thought of snow on the head of ex-winter season.
I had a flash of it.
But it was a little difficult to draw.The picture was a little difficult to draw.
The one from above.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Why did he look at it from above?
Why did you look at it from the front?
Oh, I see.
I wanted to draw a close-up of the back of the head.
That's why it ended up like this.
I should have drawn it from the front.
The thin hair is also a key point.
I thought it wouldn't show how thin the hair is from the front.
The face? Thin face?
You don't get the vibe? Probably not.
No.
No?
A musician? Are you a musician?
Oh, really?
I didn't know you were a musician.
I thought you were a TV personality.
I know you're in there somewhere, but how do you know you're a musician?
I wonder what kind of situations he's in.
Forgot my umbrella... all the time.
I've been standing in the snow all day.
Hayashi Honda, when he's standing on location in the snow
He can't rub it because it's spinning.
It's a bit melancholy.
This is very melancholy.
Back of his head
I like it.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
This is the year that represents the A word.
This time the word is
Y
Y for Y
Are you listening to me?
I am? I said...
Wai...
He's all I've got!
I'm all he's got.
But when you say it
Most people would probably think of that.
He's great!
He's a great guy.
Have you met him recently?
We met.
On a shoot.
We often ride together on shoots
On a motorcycle.
What do you mean?
Yes, we worked together.
I called Mr. Tagawa
I fucked up on the phone.
It was natural.
He told me not to talk to him like that, but I thought we were friends.
I thought we were friends.
Yeah. - Yeah.Yeah, I know.
But people in the world are like that to their superiors.
Also, the way you talk... I've been told so much,
The way you talk...
Oh, Mr. Dejima...
The way she speaks too, isn't it too much?
It's been a long time since we first met.
The program had something to do with it, too.
It was the first one.
Yes, it was.
That's for sure.
This was the beginning.
The birth of this program.
And you actually came.
It's done.
Y, please.
How is it?
It's cute.
I don't know if you've noticed this by now, but...
Degawa Tetsuro.
Hmmm...
When I say "Y," you'd think I'm talking about this guy.
The first time I co-starred with Mr. Degawa was on a show called
Degawa and Y-Girl.
There's a "Y" in that, too.
Yes.
And when we met the other day...
I think her face was like this.
I think her face was like this.It's like... it's like this here...
Mmm-hmm.
He really liked it.
What? You're fat today...
I'm kind of pudgy.
Well, it's a little late for that.
He said, "I'm kind of puffy here.
Tell him it's nothing new.
Tell her she's puffy.
Mmm-hmm.
But the whole time I'm on that camera
I don't know, I'm kind of puffy here.
It was so funny!
Mmm-hmm.
It's too late... it's too late.
I can't do anything about it now.
I've always pictured my hair like this... blondish, brownish...
No matter how many times he's on that channel, blabbing on about the time I took a cake.
Even in front of the bigwigs and the sponsors.
"He's a really bad guy.
I mean, it's really annoying.
It's really embarrassing.
Maybe some other time.
Anna's going to be on.
Knees? Knees? Kneecap?
Do you ever get tanning with your knees bare?
Do you have any clothes that just show your knees?
Inverted knees... let's kneecap.
Let's kneecap.Let's kneecap.
I'm getting sunburn on my knees. What am I supposed to do?
Sunscreen?
Have your mom put sunscreen on you.
And put some on yourself.
Then you won't get sunburnt.
And I don't go outside.
But I think you should go out.
But if I don't go outside or something...
I don't burn anymore.
I've always burned, even though I'm really dark.
I was always outside, like in elementary school.
But then I became a recluse, and the more I became a recluse, the whiter I got.
So let's become hermits.
I don't understand why they make us do sports meets and playgrounds under the hot sun.
I really don't get it.
You get burned, right?
Right?
Yes, I do.
It's too hot and I'll collapse.
Good night.
You're talking like a teacher.
And, Kuzumi, there's something else about your brother.
There's something I need to talk to you about.
Is there anything I can help you with?
My brother's mouth stinks.
It makes the house stink.
His mouth makes the house stink.
He was quite the surprise.
Maybe he should be on TV or something.Maybe you should go on TV or something.
Is there ever a day when you don't smell?
It doesn't always stink.
I really don't want anything to do with adults or people.
It's not that they stink.
It's like they do something that I don't like.
Like, I really don't get along with them.
I really don't get along with them.
I usually avoid them.
I don't get involved anymore.
I don't let them out of my sight.
Adults are like that.
Some people in society can't do that, but that's how I avoid them.
Why don't you do the same? That's what I thought.
I thought about it, but if the whole house smells bad, there's no way to avoid it.
You'll get used to it. Maybe it's better to get used to it.
You'll get used to it. You might as well get used to it.
Don't think of it as a smell in the house.
Once you accept that this is your world...
When you go out in the world
you'll realize that the world doesn't stink like this.
It will be super easy to live.
Why don't you just get used to it?
If you think it doesn't stink.
I don't mind being the big brother.
He's got a stinky mouth, and he's harassing me.
He'll make me sniff it like it's my mouth.
I'm sure of it.
Big brother.
So if you don't like it, you might as well run awayAnd if you don't like it, you might as well run away.
So you run away.
Or I'll give you something stinkier
Or give him something stinkier than your brother.
If you get beat up, you get beat up back.
You've got to have that kind of mindset.
You've got to be willing to fight back.
From here on out, we're going to make two things that stink.
When your brother comes along, you're just gonna have to do it like this.
And then you hit him with the stinky thing.
Then maybe he'll stop.
Everybody all right?
Yes, sir.
Really?
I'm glad.
Well, that's it for today. Come back and visit again.
Bye bye.
Okay.
What is this? Oh, my God.
It's funny.
Ana Channel. Subscribe to our channel.